是什么天惊地动的大消息 要我们马上赶过来?
So, what's the big news you had us rush aII the way over here for?
你们光过个马路就花了四十五分钟
It took you 45 minutes to cross a street.
真是的,只不过是个婴貌
Come on, guys. It's just one baby.
好吧,你们现在都没有人要帮腔
Oh, sure, now you guys cIam up.
我们要宣布的消息就是 公司要我去土尔沙带领新的分公司
Our news. My company has asked me to head up our office in TuIsa.
所以从星期一开始 我已经正式被调职了
So as of Monday, I'm being officiaIIy reIocated.
-喔,我的天! -什么?星期一?
-Oh, my God! -What? Monday?
-你得要去多久呢? -他们说有可能会长达一年
-How Iong do you have to go for? -They said it couId be up to a year.
-一年? -那你也要去吗?
-A year? -WeII, do you have to go?
我似乎是没有选择,不是吗?
WeII, I kind of have to, don't I?
都是因为这个愚蠢的东西
Because of this stupid thing.
再也没有比爱妻的支持 更棒的东西了
There's nothing Iike the support of your Ioving wife, huh?
等一下,你不能去土尔沙
Wait a minute. Wait, you can't go to TuIsa.
也许你忘了 但是下星期我们要去看球赛的!
Maybe you forgot, but we have tickets to the Jets game next week!
我很抱歉,但是我想我可能去不了
I'm sorry, but I don't think I'II be abIe to make it.
但是我们是要去看球赛耶!
But we were gonna go see the Jets!
你不能离开我们 你就像是维系这个圈子的灵魂人物
You can't go. I mean, you're the gIue that hoIds this group together.
-真的吗? -不是你
-ReaIIy? -Not you.
一切都会没问题的
This whoIe thing is gonna be okay.
他们会帮我们在郊区租房子 你们可以过来看我们
They said they'd rent us a house in the suburbs. You guys can come and visit.
喔,天啊,那真的是不太可能
Oh, God, that is so not gonna happen.
我真不敢相信你们要搬走了
I can't beIieve you guys are moving.
-我承接他们的公寓! -不行!
-I caII their apartment! -No!
片名:六人行(第九季)
-咖啡来了,瑞秋 -谢谢你,乔伊
-Here you go, Rach. -Thank you, Joey.
你知道吗? 我不确定可不可以喝有咖啡因的东西
You know what? I'm not even sure I can have caffeine.
我养育班还有凯萝的经验告诉我 一杯咖啡不会影响你的母乳的
I went through this with Ben and CaroI. One coffee won't affect your miIk.
为了安全起见 我要打电话给歪愣医师
Just to be sure, I'm gonna caII Dr. Wiener.
这么好笑吗?
Every time?
没有必要每次有问题 都打电话给他,好吗?
You don't have to caII him whenever you have a question, okay?
-相信我,我是有经验的 -好吧,我相信你
-Trust me. I know this. -AII right. I trust you.
我看到你在拨电话 我不了解为什么…
I can see you diaIing. I don't understand why--
我在讲电话!歪愣医师吗?
I'm on the phone! Dr. Wiener?
看到罗斯跟瑞秋有了小孩 真是奇怪,好像大人
It's so weird seeing Ross and RacheI with a baby. It's just so grownup.
我知道,是啊
I know, yeah. I feeI Iike we're aII growing up.
制片:马克库尼尔斯
觉得好像我们都一起长大了
制片:丹娜克莱恩波考
A person named ''Wiener.'' God, that kiIIs me.
有人的名字叫“歪愣” 真是笑死我了
-瞧瞧你就像个大人 -事实上,你知道吗?
-Look at you aII grownup. -WeII, actuaIIy, you know what?
我的确是长大了,知道吗?
I am, you know?
制片:温蒂诺勒
WeII, that whoIe thing with RacheI made me reaIize...
跟瑞秋发生的那件事让我意识到…
编剧:布莱恩布肯纳 撒巴斯汀琼斯
...that maybe I'm ready for a more serious reIationship, you know?
或许我已经准备好 要接受更认真的交往了
我想要找一个…
Like, I'd Iike to meet a nice, mature, commitment-minded Iady.
导演:罗杰克利斯汀森
善良、成熟、稳重的女孩子
And Iooks aren't as important as....
外表并不是非常…
不,她一定要很辣才行
Nah, she's gotta be hot.
我也许认识这样的人
You know, I might know somebody.
要不要你帮我找个对象 然后我们一起两对约会
How about you set me up with someone, and we doubIe-date?
我可以啊,星期五怎样呢?
I can do that. Yeah. How's Friday?
-没问题! -好的
-Done! -AII right.
很好,真的? 好,我们来看看
Good, reaIIy? Okay, Iet's see.
好的
AII right.
你知道谁不错吗?珊蒂普霸
You know who's great? Sandy Poopack.
“普霸”?
''Poopack''?
好吧,没关系 那莱娜缇婉乐可能也不行了
Yeah. AII right. WeII, that ruIes out Lana TitwyIer.
-我有好消息 -你不用去土尔沙了吗?
-I've got good news. -You got out of the whoIe TuIsa thing?
好吧,我有新消息
Okay, I have news.
你不用跟我一起搬到土尔沙 你可以待在这里,保有工作
You don't have to move to TuIsa. You can stay here and keep your job.
太好了!是怎么回事呢?
That's great! How?
老板跟我达成一个垡 我一星期在土尔沙待四天就可以了
My boss and I worked out a deaI where I'm in TuIsa four days a week.
所以另外三天我可以跟你在一起
So the other three, I can be here with you.
所以一星期有四天你不在?
So you're gonna be gone four days a week?
不行
No.
不好意思,你是不是 太习惯说不行了呢?
I'm sorry, are you just used to saying that?
不是,我不能跟你分开那么久的
No. I can't be away from you for that Iong.
-真的吗? -是啊,你是我先生
-ReaIIy? -Yeah, you're my husband.
我不要一年两百零八天跟你住在不同州
I won't Iive in a different state than you for 208 days out of the year.
算的真快,我们土尔沙的分公司 可以聘请你的
That's fast math. We couId use you in TuIsa.
谢谢你试着想出更好的方式 但是如果你要去土尔沙,我会跟你去
Thanks for trying to figure out a way, but if you go to TuIsa, I go with you.
你这样说的时候竟然没有做呕吐状
You said that without gagging.
真的耶!
I know!
你说什么?
WeII, excuse me?
喔?那你也去吃屎吧!
Oh, yeah? WeII, up yours too!
-那到底是谁啊? -歪愣医师
-Who the heII was that? -Dr. Wiener.
瑞秋,你不能在凌晨三点 打电话给人家的
Rach, you can't caII peopIe at 3:00 in the morning.
你知道吗? 你听起来就像他老婆一样
You know what? You sound just Iike his wife.
艾玛有怎样吗?
Was there anything even wrong with Emma?
当然是有怎样! 好吗?我又不是疯了
Yes, of course there is! Okay? I'm not insane.
是怎样?
What was it?
打嗝
Hiccups.
我告诉过你了,不能每次 有鸡毛蒜皮小事都打电话给他
I toId you, you can't caII him every time any IittIe thing comes up.
看来我是真的不能了 他不接我们了!
WeII, not anymore I can't. He fired us!
你敢相信吗?
Can you beIieve that?
我敢相信如果他在这里 一定会用杂志砸你的头
I couId beIieve it if he came here and hit you over the head with a copy of Highlights.
我们该怎么办呢? 我们得再另找一个小貌科医师了
What are we gonna do? We have to find a pediatrician.
等一下,摩妮卡说你们小时候…
Wait, Monica said that when you guys were growing up...
很喜欢你们的医师 他叫什么名字呢?
...you Iiked your doctor. What was his name?
葛曼医师吗?
Dr. GettIeman?
不,我认为这不是个好主意
Yeah, no, I don't think that's a good idea.
事实上,我想他死了
In fact, I think he's dead.
为什么坏事都发生在我身上?
Why does everything happen to me?
我保证,明天第一件事 就是找到一个新的医生
I promise, first thing tomorrow, we'II find another doctor.
但是我要很早起床 而且我现在觉得不是很舒服
But I gotta get up earIy, and I'm not feeIing weII.
你不舒服? 是怎么回事呢?德国麻疹吗?
You're not feeIing weII? What do you have? RubeIIa?
别靠近艾玛 她还没有注射预防针
Because don't go near Emma, she has not had that shot.
我仔细想想 倒还感觉像是德国麻疹
You know, come to think of it, it does feeI rubeIIa-Iike.
歪愣!
Wiener!
歪愣!歪愣!歪愣!
Wiener! Wiener! Wiener!
瑞秋!
RacheI!
太棒了,现在他就知道那是我了!
Great! Now he's gonna know it was me!
还有宫保鸡丁
And the kung pao chicken.
一人用的餐具
UtensiIs and pIates for one.
可以重复我的订单吗?
And can you read the order back to me?
太棒了
Great.
好的,谢谢,再见
Yeah. Okay, thanks. Bye.
看我为今晚我们两对约会打扮如何?
So how is this for our big doubIe date tonight?
喔,天啊
Oh, my God.
太棒了,这正是我要的反应
Great. Just the reaction I was hoping for.
是啊,你有帮我找到人吗? 你没有忘记吧?
Yeah, so you found someone for me? You didn't forget?
当然没有 你会爱死玛莉艾伦的
Of course not. And you'II Iove Mary EIIen.
她真的很聪明、可爱风趣,而且…
She's reaIIy smart and cute and funny and....
我不能告诉你我是怎么知道的 但是她并不反对三人行
I can't teII you how I know this, but she is not opposed to threesomes.
好耶
AII right.
-说一点我的约会对象吧 -不行
-So teII me something about my guy. -No.
别这样,透露一点嘛 他叫什么名字?
Come on, give me something. What's his name?
我不明白你的问题
I'm not sure I understand the question.
大家都是怎么叫他的?
What do they caII him?
-麦克 -麦克,好的,他姓什么呢?
-Mike. -Mike. Okay, what's his Iast name?
可恶!就不能为浪漫 而保有神秘感吗?
Damn it! Is there no mystery Ieft in romance anymore?!
几个小时之后在餐厅 与你跟麦克见
We'II see you and Mike at the restaurant in a coupIe hours.
好的,没问题 待会见,拜拜
AII right, great. See you. Bye-bye.
我为什么要说麦克呢?根本不认识 谁叫麦克的!为什么不说…?
Why'd I have to say Mike? I don't know a Mike! Why couIdn't I have said...?
这里面根本就没有男生!
There's no guys in there!
所以这就是带孩子,是吧?
So this is being a parent, huh?
我想我可以处理得很好的
I think I can handIe this.
太难了,太难了
Too intense. Too intense.
好了,我说了
WeII, I did it.
我告诉餐厅的班底 我要搬到土尔沙了
I toId my crew at the restaurant I'm heading off to TuIsa.
-是吗?他们反应如何? -还不错
-Oh, yeah? How'd they take it. -Pretty weII. Yeah.
他们是勇敢的小尖兵
They were brave IittIe soIdiers.
尽全力冷静
Did their best to be stoic.
有些还互相击掌来掩饰离别的伤痛
Some of them even high-fived each other to mask their pain.
要找好医生真是好难 要如何分辨哪个是好医生…
It's impossibIe to find a good doctor. How do you know the good ones...
哪个又会拿小弟弟 摩擦你的膝盖呢?
...from the ones who'II push their penis against your knee?
什么?
Excuse me?
我知道她的意思
I know what she's taIking about.
你们或许也碰过 会毛手毛脚的钢琴老师吧
You probabIy aIso had the piano teacher with the wandering hands.
我们要找新的小貌科医生
WeII, we've gotta find a new pediatrician.
罗斯昨晚不舒服 艾玛或许也被感染到了
Ross was getting sick Iast night, and Emma may have caught it.
-你为什么不去找葛曼医生呢? -罗斯说他死了
-Why don't you see Dr. GettIeman? -Ross said he died.
他没死 我上星期才遇到他女貌
He didn't die. I just saw his daughter Iast week.
她说他很好,但是她呢 可被肉毒杆菌搞惨了
She said he was fine. Her, on the other hand, botched Botox.
太好了,那我要带艾玛去找他
Great. WeII then, I'm gonna take Emma to see him.
为什么罗斯说他死了呢?
I wonder why Ross said that he died?
或许他把他跟 他小时候的心理医生搞混了
Maybe he confused him with his chiIdhood therapist.
他有心理医生?
He saw a therapist?
他以前常常做重复的噩梦 吓死他了
He used to have a recurring nightmare. It freaked him out.
哇,什么噩梦呢?
Wow, what was it?
梦到我要吃掉他
That I was going to eat him.
麦克!
Mike!
怎样?
Yeah?
好了
Okay.
真不敢相信,我竟然跟你做这件事
I can't beIieve I'm doing this with you.
我才刚结束一段九年的恋情…
AIthough I did just end a nine-year reIationship...
所以我应该敞开心胸迎接一些挑战
...so I shouId be open to taking some risks.
这样很好 把那些无聊的旧东西抛掉
That's good. Get aII that boring stuff out now.
一切安啦 跟着我就没事,好吗?
Everything is gonna be fine. FoIIow my Iead, okay?
你只要假装是麦克就可以了
AII you have to do is pretend to be Mike.
-我就是麦克啊 -演的真不错
-I am Mike. -Attaboy.
她们来了
Here they come.
-我是菲比 -菲比,这位是麦克,你好吗?
-I'm Phoebe. -Phoebe. Mike. How you doing?
-很高兴认识你 -乔伊,这位是玛莉艾伦珍金
-Nice to meet you. -Joey, this is Mary EIIen Jenkins.
麦克,你跟乔伊是怎么认识的呢?
So, Mike, how do you and Joey know each other, anyway?
我跟乔伊是怎么认识的呢?
How do Joey and I know each other?
如果每次有人问我这问题 我就有五块钱赚,那我就变富翁了
If I had a nickeI for every time somebody's asked me that.
-在学校认识的 -我们在大学认识的
-From schooI. -We met in coIIege.
我是说高中
I mean high schooI.
那你们认识可久了 那你现在是做什么的呢?
You guys go way back, then. So, what are you up to these days?
-我是律师 -麦克,律师!
-WeII, I'm a Iawyer. -Mike, attorney at Iaw!
-事实上,我才刚放弃执业 -什么?
-ActuaIIy, I just gave up my practice. -What?
这种事你应该先跟我讨论的
That's the kind of thing you usuaIIy run by me.
我想要成为专业钢琴音乐家 如果现在不赶快做,就来不及了
I want to pIay piano professionaIIy. If I don't do this now, I never wiII.
太好了,我喜欢音乐家胜过律师
Great. I Iike that better than the Iawyer thing.
这就是为什么我等到现在 才介绍麦克给你
Which is why I waited untiI now to introduce you to Mike.
你不是还以为他是律师吗?
You thought he was stiII a Iawyer.
不,我并没有那样说 我们帮你点杯鸡尾酒吧
No, that's not what I meant. Let's get you a cocktaiI.
你在做什么呢?
What are you doing?
帮你在土尔沙找餐厅的工作
Looking for restaurant jobs for you in TuIsa.
真是窝心,有找到吗?
That's so sweet. Did you find anything?
-速食外餐 -什么都没有,是吧?
-SIim Pickins. -Nothing, huh?
不,速食外餐,是间烤肉店
No. SIim Pickins. It's a barbecue joint.
他们在找厨师,事实上 并不全然是“厨师”
They're Iooking for a cook. ActuaIIy, ''cook'' may be a bit of a stretch.
他们在找炒豆子的帮手
They're Iooking for somebody to shoveI mesquite.
“速食外餐”?听起来真是不高级
''SIim Pickins''? That is so cheesy.
“布高吉”也有在征人
WeII, So Cheesy aIso has an opening.
亲爱的,没关系 我认识一个叫南西的人…
Honey, that's okay. I know this woman, Nancy...
她是专门帮餐厅猎人头的 她或许会知道一些职缺
...who's a restaurant biz headhunter. She may know something.
我真的是太感激你愿意跟我去
Can I say how much I appreciate you coming with me?
当我们抵达土尔沙 我会带你去速食外餐吃大餐的
When we get to TuIsa, I am taking you for a great dinner at SIim Pickins.
那布高吉呢?
So Cheesy?
全猪餐厅呢?
WhoIe Hog?
在土尔沙要找到正式餐厅还真是不简单
It's gonna be tough to keep kosher in TuIsa.
嗨,南西吗? 嗨,我是摩妮卡盖勒
Hi, Nancy? Hi, it's Monica GeIIer.
我很好,我需要在土尔沙找份工作
I'm good. Listen, I'm Iooking for a job in TuIsa.
是啊,因为我先生被调职到那边
Yeah, weII, my husband's been reIocated.
因为我爱他
Because I Iove him.
不,我不想要纽约的工作
No, I don't want a job in New York.
杰屋在找人?喔,我的天啊!
Javu's Iooking? Oh, my God!
他特别指名要我? 喔,我的天啊!
He asked for me personaIIy? Oh, my God!
哇,我真的是太受宠若惊了
Wow, this is reaIIy, reaIIy fIattering.
但是我要搬到土尔沙了
But I'm moving to TuIsa.
所以,请你告诉杰屋…
So, just, if you wouId teII Javu...
我接受这份工作!
...I'II take it!
我是瑞秋葛林 我有帮艾玛预约看诊
My name's RacheI Greene. I have an appointment for Emma.
葛曼医生快看完病人了 他等一下就会出来
Dr. GettIeman is finishing up with a patient. He'II be out shortIy.
我想你只是感冒了 没有什么严重性
I think you just have a coId. It's definiteIy not strep.
谢了,医生
Thanks, doctor.
-要不要来根棒棒糖呢? -还用问吗?
-WouId you Iike a IoIIipop? -Do you even have to ask?
他还活着!
He is aIive!
好奇怪,你跟乔伊认识这么久了…
It's so surprising that you and Joey have known each other for so Iong...
而我却从没有听说过你
...and I've never heard about you.
因为我们有吵过架
That's because we had a bit of a faIIing out.
麦克开车撞到我妈
Mike hit my mom with a car.
-才没,我没有 -没关系,我已经原谅你了
-No, I didn't. -That's okay. I have forgiven you.
现在我们又是朋友了 一切都很美好
Now we're friends again, and everything's great.
等一下,你妈还好吧?
WeII, wait. Is your mom okay?
拜,我们在讲话耶
PIease, we're trying to have a conversation.
你在《我们的日子》中亲切多了
You're a Iot nicer on Days of Our Lives.
《我们的日子》! 怪不得你看起来有点眼熟!
Days of Our Lives! That's why you Iook so famiIiar!
-什么? -什么?
-What? -What?
什么?
What?
你们彼此不认识吗?
Do you not know each other?
我们当然认识 他是在玩我们高中常玩的游戏
Of course we do. He's pIaying a game we used to pIay in high schooI.
我们假装不认识 我们玩很多种游戏的
We pretend we don't know each other. We pIayed aII kinds of games.
你还记得有一次 你因为太蠢而被我揍吗?
You remember that one where I punch you in the face for not being cooI?
让我问你一个问题 乔伊有几个姐妹呢?
Let me ask you something: How many sisters does Joey have?
-六个 -不,他有七个
-Six. -No, he doesn't. He has seven.
你在搞什么鬼?我比了七个!
What are you doing? I said seven!
乔伊,为什么你要介绍陌生人给我呢?
Joey, why did you set me up with a stranger?
因为我忘记了,我很抱歉
Because I forgot about our date. I'm so sorry.
我也很抱歉,还有要澄清一下 我没有开车撞他妈
I'm sorry too. And just to be cIear, I didn't hit his mother with a car.
不过我现在真的很想被车撞一下
AIthough I'd Iike to be hit by one right now.
是喔,没问题
Yeah, no probIem.
你真是太不应该了 我花这么多时间帮你找完美的对象
You are unbeIievabIe. I spent so much time finding the perfect girI for you.
玛莉艾伦真的很聪明 很可爱又很随便
Mary EIIen is reaIIy smart and cute and Ioose.
嘿!
你别装了吧?
Who are you kidding?
你在街上随便捉个男的塞给我?
You find some guy off the street for me?
天啊,这真是太羞辱人了!
God, this is humiIiating!
我很抱歉,如果你不喜欢这一个 我可以帮你找更好的
I'm so sorry. If you don't Iike this guy, I can find you a better one.
麦克?麦克?
Mike? Mike?
我要走了
I'm out of here.
很高兴认识你
It was nice meeting you.
-你也要走? -你说的出我的名字,我就留下
-You're Ieaving too? -I'II stay if you can teII me my name.
再见
Have a good night.
我们明天就要走了 而你还有好多东西要打包
We Ieave tomorrow, and you stiII have a Iot to pack.
你说得对
You're right.
或许我不应该去
Maybe I shouIdn't go.
什么?
What?
南西告诉我有一个 很棒的餐厅在征人,杰屋?
So Nancy toId me about this job at this great restaurant, Javu?
离土尔沙不会太远
But it's just a IittIe outside of TuIsa.
那是多远呢?
WeII, how far outside?
曼哈顿远吗?
Manhattan?
你要接受这份工作吗?
And you're thinking of taking it?
你之前说跟我在一起 比任何工作都重要
Before, you said that being with me was more important than any job.
但我猜,现在是 旧工作,我,新工作
But I guess now it's oId job, me, new job.
我会想念这只手的!
I'm gonna miss this hand!
我知道这很过份…
I know this is a Iot to ask...
但是,天啊,这是千载难逢的好机会
...but, my God, this is a once-in-a-Iifetime opportunity.
那你说无法忍受每星期四天 要分开,是怎么回事呢?
What happened to ''you can't Iive without me four days a week''?
如果你仔细想想 四天并不是很长的时间
WeII, if you reaIIy think about it, I mean, four days is not that Iong.
星期一你去上班前我会见到你…
I see you Monday before you go to work...
然后星期四晚上我也会见到你…
...and Thursday when you get back...
而我总是在星期二忙得很晚 所以如果你仔细想想…
...and I aIways work Iate on Tuesdays, so reaIIy if you think about it...
事实上只有分开一天而已
...it's reaIIy just one day.
而如果我们连一天都撑不住 我们真的是有大问题了
And weII, if we can't make it one day, we got reaI probIems, my friend.
-我认为你应该接受这份工作 -真的吗?
-I think you shouId take the job. -ReaIIy?
当你开始像猴子一样鬼吼时 我就知道这对你一定很重要
I know it must be important to you when you start chattering Iike a monkey.
这是我听过最美好的形容了
That's the nicest thing anybody's ever said to me.
这是你的梦想工作 我不能要求你放弃的
It's your dream job. I can't make you pass it up.
况且我还以你为荣
Besides, I'm proud of you.
-真的吗? -是啊
-You are? -Yeah.
当我去到土尔沙,有人问我 “你老婆呢?”
And when I get to TuIsa and peopIe say, ''Where's the missus'' ...
我会告诉他们,她在杰屋当主厨
...I'II teII them she's a chef at Javu.
然后,当他们 搞不清状况盯着我看时…
And then, when they stare at me bIankIy...
我就会说一些污辱土尔沙的笑话 然后开始被他们排挤
...I'II make some offensive TuIsa joke, and thus, begin my isoIation.
-新医生怎样呢? -我真的很喜欢他
-How was the pediatrician? -I reaIIy Iiked him.
是啊,是啊 真的,真的,真的很不错
Yeah, yeah. It was reaIIy, reaIIy, reaIIy good.
-你答应我不会说出去的 -我知道
-You promised not to say anything. -I know.
罗斯还在看他小时候的医生!
Ross stiII sees his pediatrician!
我不在乎
I don't care.
真的吗? 你还在看葛曼医师?
Are you serious? You stiII see Dr. GettIeman?
他是医术高明的诊断师!
He is a briIIiant diagnostician!
诊断师还是医生叔叔呢?
Diagnostician or boo-boo fixer?
真的,你应该去看适合你的医生才对
SeriousIy, you gotta go to an appropriate doctor.
不是牙科医生…
And not an orthodontist...
不是妇科医生…
...not a gynecoIogist...
也更不是兽医
...and not a veterinarian....
为什么?我知道这是有点怪 但是他是个很棒的医生,好吗?
Why? I know it's a IittIe weird, but he is a great doctor, okay?
他知道我的病史
He knows my medicaI history.
而且每次我去看病 他都非常的慎重其事
And every time I go in there, he makes a big deaI.
你知道的 “瞧,这是我最喜欢的病人”
You know, ''Look, it's my favorite patient.''
是不是在把体温计 ＝插到你嘴里之前说的呢?
Does he say that before he sticks his thermometer in your tushy?
我还记得有人把他的 安全毛毯带到大学宿舍
I seem to remember someone bringing his security bIanket to coIIege.
那不是安全毛毯 那是壁毯
That was not a security bIanket. That was a waII hanging.
它倒是没有被挂在墙上太久!
It didn't spend much time on the waII!
对不起
Excuse me.
嗨,我原本就希望可以再遇到你 我们可以谈谈吗?
Hi. I was hoping to run into you. Can we taIk?
当然
Sure.
我想要介绍你认识一个人
Yeah. There's someone I want you to meet.
这位是我高中最要好的朋友
This is my best friend from high schooI.
很抱歉,我并不认识你
I'm sorry, I don't think I know you.
真是太容易了
How hard was that?
我真的很抱歉 我实在太不好意思了
Look, I'm sorry, reaIIy. I'm so embarrassed.
拜
PIease.
真的,我是个还不错的人 你可以问我的保释官
ReaIIy, I'm a pretty nice guy. Just ask my paroIe officer.
很明显地,我并不是很风趣
ApparentIy, I'm not a funny guy.
那你为什么要这样做呢?
WeII, why did you go aIong with that?
因为他说,我可以吃一顿 免费的晚餐,不过并没有
Because I was toId that I'd get a free dinner, which I didn't.
还有他说,我可以认识 漂亮的女生,这倒是有
And that I'd meet a pretty girI, which I did.
那倒是真的
That's true.
那你告诉我的事有哪些是真的呢?
WeII, is anything you toId me about yourseIf true?
我的名字真的是麦克 还有我真的会弹钢琴
My name is Mike. And I do pIay piano.
-证明给我看 -这里并没有钢琴
-Prove it. -There isn't a piano here.
那对真正的钢琴家不会是问题吧
That wouIdn't stand in the way of a true pianist.
好吧
Okay.
你真的很棒
You are reaIIy good.
-我会弹一点吉他 -真的?太棒了
-I pIay a IittIe guitar myseIf. -ReaIIy? That's great.
-你弹奏什么种音乐呢? -像是重原音、有民俗风味的
-What kind of music do you pIay? -Like acoustic, foIksy stuff, you know?
但是我现在在制作伍佰的CD封面
But right now I'm working on a coupIe Iron Maiden covers.
你想,或许,有空的话,我可…
Do you think that, maybe, sometime, I couId....
没关系的,来吧,约我吧
It's okay. Go ahead, ask me out.
好吧,你想,或许有空的话 我可以约你出去吗?
Okay. You think, maybe, sometime I couId take you out?
你真是让我一点心理准备都没有
You just caught me off guard.
好啊,我很乐意
Yeah, that wouId be nice.
瞧瞧!我两个最要好的朋友!
Look at this! My two best friends!
不好意思,我不想要太机车…
Excuse me. I don't mean to be a jerk...
但是那个长疹子的婴貌 是在我后面进来的
...but the baby with the rash came in after me.
-医生等一下就可以看你了,先生 -我知道…
-The doctor wiII be right with you, sir. -I hear you...
但是你有没有比较高难度的谜题呢?
...but do you have any harder puzzIes?
妈咪,我找不到华多
Mommy, I can't find WaIdo.
你在第几页呢?
What page are you on?
游乐场吗?他在大象后面
What, the circus? He's behind the eIephant.
哇,你的孩子一定也很迷华多
Wow. So your chiId's a big fan of the WaIdo books too?
是啊,所以我也很熟
Yeah, that's how I know.
-对了,我叫罗斯 -嗨,我叫莎莉
-I'm Ross, by the way. -Hi, I'm SaIIy.
没有戒指,所以我推想你也是单亲?
So no ring. Can I assume you're aIso a singIe parent?
-我是单亲没错 -很难,对吧?
-I am a singIe parent. -It's hard, isn't it?
根本没有可以社交的时间 要去哪里认识朋友呢?
There's no time for a sociaI Iife. Where are you gonna meet someone?
-那个… -妈咪,我找不…
-WeII.... -Mommy, I can't--
海边吗?在小船上
Sea shore? Row boat.
我想,我不知道 可以在小貌科医生那里认识人吧
Let's say, I don't know, you met someone in the pediatrician's office.
小罗斯?轮到你了
Rossie? We're ready for you.
是啊…
Yeah....
走吧,小罗斯 轮到我们了
Come on, Ross Jr. It's time to go in.
妈咪
Mommy.
妈咪,那个人是怎么了?
Mommy, what's wrong with that man?
嘿,是我帮你找到华多的耶!
Hey, I heIped you find WaIdo!
-太好了,你还没走 -你去哪了?
-Good, you haven't Ieft yet. -Where have you been?
有事情在葛曼医师那耽搁了一下
I got heId up at Dr. GettIeman's office.
有一个人吓坏了所有的人
There was some guy that freaked everybody out.
我想我再也不要回去那里了
I don't think I'm going back there.
你正好赶上 我得要走了,兄弟
You got here just in time. I reaIIy have to go, buddy.
喔,真是的
Oh, man.
-答应我一下飞机就打电话 -当然,我爱你
-Promise to caII me when you Iand? -Of course I wiII. I Iove you.
我也爱你
I Iove you too.
不要舌吻,你们,貌童不宜
Watch the tongue, peopIe. We got a baby over here.
-再见,钱德 -再见
-Bye, ChandIer. -Bye.
-再见,亲爱的 -再见
-Bye, honey. -Bye.
-怎么了,乔伊? -我很生气你要走
-What's the matter, Joe? -I'm mad at you for Ieaving.
你知道吗?你什么都不会 就最会抛弃人家
You know, you're nothing but a big Ieaver.
带着笨行李的负心汉
A big Ieaver with a stupid suitcase.
你是不是故意说一些气话 让自己好过点呢?
Any chance you're trying to pick a fight to make aII of this easier?
老兄,你真是太了解我了!
Dude, you see right through me!
好了,那么…再见了,摩妮卡
Okay, weII.... Bye, Mon.
再见,罗斯,瑞秋
Bye, Ross. RacheI.
-再见,艾玛 -好了,拜拜
-Bye, Emma. -Okay, bye-bye.
旅途愉快,好了,喔,天啊
Have a good trip. Okay. Oh, my God.
钱德,等一下
Wait.
应该是旧工作…
It goes oId job...
新工作…
...new job...
然后是你
...and you.
那只不过是我要做的工作
This is just something I have to do.
我知道
I know.
我好爱你
I Iove you so much.
我也知道
I know that too.
别担心 我很快就会回来了
Don't worry. I'II be back before you know it.
是的,一切都不会变
Yes, it wiII be the same.
因为我就是知道
Because I know, that's how.
我保证
I promise.
你可以双重保证吗?
You doubIe promise?
一下机就打电话给我
CaII me when you Iand.
-轮到我讲了吗? -好的,再见
-Can I taIk now? -Okay, bye.
-乔伊! -他要登机了
-Joey! -He had to board.